contentbuzz.com 2013-09-23

# ContentBuzz.com - Privacy Policy

ContentBuzz.com Privacy Policy 

Introduction 

We at ContentBuzz.com are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. ContentBuzz.com has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. 

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information.

ContentBuzz.com strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, ContentBuzz.com intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this online privacy policy.

Cookies 

Some of our web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking systems. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about web site activity. Some cookies and other technology may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the web site. 

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our web site and your web experience. 

Security 

Wherever your Personal Information may be held within ContentBuzz.com or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

Your Agreement 

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our online privacy policy and to ContentBuzz.com processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above
